3w.clo3d-china.com
First, open our Chinese official website, 3w.clo3d-china.com.
Because the mobile phone and WeChat browsers are easy to lose the page, it is recommended to use the computer to open it.
Recommend iChrome and other mainstream browsers.
Click the login button, then click the login button in the login page.
Enter your email password and mobile phone number.
After receiving the mobile phone verification code, click Verify.
Click Create Account and verify as a real person.
Next, please go to your registered email and receive the verification email.
Congratulations, you have successfully registered your account.
You can click on the upper right corner of the website to check your account details.
If you no longer use the following, you can sign up.
Thank you.
If you want to sign up for the free application, please click the blue Free Application button.
Click Download and start the free application for 14 days.
The latest version of the software will automatically be downloaded.
After downloading the software, double-click to install the software.
Click the Download button to install the software.
After the installation is complete, you can see the blue software icon on the desktop.
Double-click to open it and click the black login button.
On the jumping login page, please click the Chinese user login button.
As you have already logged in to the Chinese official website, you can directly click to log in as in the video.
If you need to re-login, you only need to enter your email address and password.
Enjoy your design journey!